Matt Fazza

Software Engineer

(972)795-3961

matthewfazza@yahoo.c

Denver, CO

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mattfazza

https://www.github.com/mattfazza

https://www.mattfazza.c om

PROFILE

My name is Matt Fazza, a software engineer who just moved to Denver, CO. I have worked with data engineering, DevOps, and full-stack web –that's what I want to get back to. I have been working on my **React/Redux** skills for some time now, and I'm ready to make the shift to a **Front-end / Full-stack** stack position. I'm primarily a problem-solver, and professionally I always focus on adding as much value as possible, as fast as possible. I write code on my free time as well (from Alexa skills to **React** apps, and **open-source contributions**), but I find my work/life balance through running, playing music, and taking care of my dogs.

EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer – CTG DevOps & Automation, Fidelity Investments; Dallas, TX — October 2018 – March 2019

I was tasked with setting up **Jenkins** slaves and setting up pipelines (as code - **CICD**). I was also responsible for creating server-side configurations in both **Linux** and Windows servers. Another responsibility of mine was containerizing applications and pipeline stages. Parallel to these projects, I wrote **python** frameworks on the automation side (mostly for **Spark** and **MongoDB**).

Software Engineer – CTG Metrics, Fidelity Investments; Dallas, TX — October 2018 — December 2018

Lead automation team in project to automate the process of collecting metrics about applications continuously integrated with **Jenkins**. Every night, the script makes calls to the Jenkins **API**. The response contains information about all stages of the builds, and the application's continuous deployment and integration. After collecting the information, the script inserts it into **MongoDB**. **Tableau** reports are generated from what is in the database to report mean time to recover, cycle time, success/failure rate and other metrics. Here, I lead code reviews, and collaborated with the team through agile to write the **scripts**.

Software Engineer – Disaster Recovery Tool, Fidelity Investments; Raleigh, NC – June 2018 – October 2018

On my first project with Fidelity, I worked on a full-stack web-application with an agile team. It was intended to allow brokers to log in trades when systems go down. Along with my team, I refactored an old frontend into a single-page application in **Angular**, wrote some of the **Java** (**Spring**) middletier to connect the MDM backend, and implemented git strategy.

Software Engineer, Food Blockchain, The Fellows Group LLC Name; Dallas, TX – January 2018 – May 2018

In the beginning of my last semester in college, I was brought in to work on a blockchain application to track the provenance of produce. As part of the UTD **Blockchain** Club, I was already familiar on how to write applications for the **Etherium** Blockchain. I was responsible for writing smart contracts in Solidity, and collaborating with the team in an agile (scrum) fashion.

EDUCATION

The University of Texas at Dallas – Dallas, TX — 2013-2018 Bachelor's degree in Software Engineering.

SKILLS

Python, MongoDB, Express, React, Node, Java, C, C++, Swift, Javascript, Typescript, Solidity, Truffle, Angular, HTML, CSS, MySQL, Bash, JIRA, GIT, Sourcetree, Bitbucket, Jenkins, AWS, Docker, XCode, Atom, VSCode, Eclipse, MacOS, Linux, Windows.